# Adam Galt B.Sc.

Systems Administrator DevOps Cloud Engineer

Email: adam@galt.me

Website: galt.me

Blog: blog.galt.me

Github: AdamGalt

# Key skills

Debian / Red Hat / Ubuntu / Windows

Docker, VMWare, Meraki, Fortigate

Zabbix, Wireguard, Netdata, Veeam

Ansible, Terraform, Bash, Python

AWS, EC2, S3, DigitalOcean, Hetzner

NGINX, Apache2, HTML, CSS, GIT

System Spec and Solution Architecture

System Building and Repair

**Troubleshooting and Projects** 

**ITIL Certified** 

### **Interests**

Automation and IOT

**Automotive Mechanics** 

Motorcycle Adventures

Android Lineage ROM Testing

## **Summary**

Conscientious, hardworking individual with the highest values of integrity and morals. Well-rounded character with the ability to ally professional qualifications with practical experience.

I am an experienced System Administrator and support provider able to flexibly integrate into roles. Working independently, or as part of a unit and serve as a team leader when required. I am accustomed to working under pressure, meeting deadlines and strive for attention to detail. I hold a full, clean driving license for cars and motorcycles.

## **Experience**

**2022 – Present:** PA Media Group, Stream DevOps Team. DevOps Engineer for a multi-national media company. Working closely with the development pods to ensure that releases are engineered and deployed correctly. Cloud infrastructure provisioning and service maintenance, alongside incident investigations, process automation, design and development. Focusing on championing security, CI/CD lifecycles and systems administration best practices. Mainly working with AWS, Terraform, Jenkins and various Linux environment.

**2021-2022:** University of Oxford, Radcliffe Department of Medicine, Weatherall Institute of Molecular Medicine. Systems Administrator to the WIMM. Responsible for building and maintaining a diverse, cross-platform, multi-site research infrastructure in the 'imm' domain. Design, development and deployment of new systems, services and tools. Automation and orchestration of systems using Ansible, Bash, Python and PowerShell.

**2018 – 2021**: University of Oxford, Department of Engineering Science, Information Engineering Group Linux Systems Administrator of the "robots" domain for the Information Engineering group. Responsible for building, configuring and maintenance of data, infrastructure and project servers. Building and repair of custom GPU compute desktops. Management of networks and a range of workstations (Linux, Mac and some Windows). Backup implementation as well as trial, deploy, roll-out and debug of new software. Technical appraisals of system requirements in cutting edge research environments. Resolution of non-standard problems.

#### **Education**

2022 - DevOps Course - Codecademy

2019 - Red Hat Certified System Administrator

2019 - ITIL Foundation Certification in IT Service Management

2017 – Java Course- Codecademy

2013 - Oxford Brookes University – IT Multimedia Production – B.Sc. (Hons.)